AD.MC.012
AbuDhabi
- Woman with flowers in her hair in a long light-colored dress with floral embroidery. 29.4 x 19.5 cm, Undated; Studio Photo Abel, Constantinople (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Embroidery; Flowers; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewellery; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women